ο Θεός της ηχάριτης,
Κύριε Λέησον,
της Παναγίας Αχράτου,
υπερευλογημένης ενδόξου,
δεσποινήσιμον Θεοτόκου
και αϊπαρθένου Μαρίας,
μεταπάντων των Αγίων
γημονεύσαντες,
εαυτούς και αλλήλους
και πάσα την ζωήν ημών,
Χριστό το Θεό
παραθώμεθα.
Συγκύριε
Ο της Σοντοκράτος και σου έστειν η Βασιλεία και η δύναμης και η δόξα του Πατρός και του Υιού και του Αγίου Πνεύματος νυν και αη και εις τους αιώνας των αιώνων.
Αμήν, ο Εύσχημον Ιωσήφ από του ξύλου καθελών του άχραντών σου σώμα.
Συνδώνει καθαρά η λύστας και αρώμασιν, ενήματι και νόκυδεύσας απέθετο,
αλλά τριήμερος ανέστης Κύριε παρέχον το κόσμο το μεγαέλαιο.
Δόξα Πατρή και Υωκή Αγιοπνεύματι τες μυροφόρης γυνέξη παρά το μνήμα επιστά.
Amen.
Thank you.
For you alone are holy, you alone are Lord Jesus Christ, to the glory of God the Father. Amen.
Every day will I bless you, and I will praise your name forever, and unto the ages of ages.
O Lord, to the Lord.
us this day without sin.
Blessed are you, O Lord, the God of our fathers, and praise and glorify His pure name unto
the ages.
Amen.
Let your mercy, O Lord, be upon us, even when we have hoped in you.
Blessed are you, O Lord Jesus.
I said, O Lord, have mercy on me.
You, my son.
for I have sinned against you.
O Lord, to you have I fled for refuge.
Teach me to do your will, for you are my God.
For in you is the fountain of life.
In your life we shall see lie.
Continue your mercy unto those who are not.
Holy God, holy, mighty, holy, mortal, have mercy on us.
O ye God, holy man.
O ye immortal, have mercy on us.
Glory to the Father, and to the Son, and to the Holy Spirit, both now and ever, and unto
the ages of ages.
Amen.
Holy and mortal have mercy
Holy God,
Holy
Oh
Immortal, have mercy on us.
Σήμερον σωτηρία το κόσμο γεγονέων σου με το αναστάθει εκτράβου και αρχηγό της ζωής υμών.
Καθελών γαρμών θανάτων των θάνατων, τον οίκος εδώ και νήμιν και το μεγαέλαιο.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Αμήν
Υπέρ της άνωθεν ειρήνης και της σωτηρίας των ψυχώνημων του Κυρίου Δεηθώμες.
Κύριε Δεηθώμες.
Υπέρ της ειρήνης του σημαντός κόσμου ευσταθίας των Αγίων του Θεού Εκκλησιών
και της των πάντων ενώσεως του Κυρίου Δεηθώμες.
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
Υπέρ του Αγίου Υφού Του και των μεταπίστεων σε βλαβιάς και φόβου Θεό Ισιοντών εν Αυτόν του Κυρίου Ρεϊθώμεν.
Κύριε θέλευ εισόν
Πέραν των ευσεβών και ορθοδόξων χριστιανών
Κύριου δε ηθόμεν
Κύριε Ειστον, υπέρ του Αρχιεπισκόπου ήμων Νικολάου,
του τιμίου Πρεστητερίου της Εγχριστώ διακονίας παντών του κλήνου και του λαού,
Σκύριου δε Ιθόμα!
Let us pray.
to the Lord.
Lord have
mercy.
For favorable weather, for an abundance
of the fruits of the earth
and for peaceful times
let us pray to the Lord.
Lord
have mercy.
For those
who travel by land, sea and
air, for the sick,
the suffering, the captives and for
their salvation, let us
Thank you.
Let us pray to the Lord.
Lord, have mercy.
For our deliverance from all affliction, wrath, danger, and necessity,
let us pray to the Lord.
Lord, have mercy.
Help us, save us, have mercy upon us,
Keep us, O God, by your grace
for your have mercy.
Memorating our most holy, pure,
blessed and glorious lady,
the Theodokos and ever, Virgin Mary,
together with all the saints,
with us commend our children,
one another,
and the whole life of Christ our God.
To you, O Lord.
For to you belong, O glory,
honor and worship,
to the Lord.
The Father and the Son and the Holy Spirit, now and forever and to the ages of ages.
Amen.
Bless the Lord, O my soul, and all that is within me. Bless his holy name.
Through the intercessions of the Theodokal Savior, save us.
The Lord has prepared his throne in the heavens, and his kingdom rules over all.
Through the intercessions of the Theodokos, Savior, and the Holy Spirit,
Υπότιτλοι AUTHORWAVE
A gift for the presents.
Presents.
Oh my goodness, we're giving presents now.
Wow.
And let's see.
What would you prefer?
What kind of present do you want for Christmas?
I don't know.
You don't know.
What do you want for Christmas?
A lapar.
A lot.
Top, you said?
What do you want?
You don't know.
What do you want for Christmas?
Well, you're going to buy presents for people.
What are you going to get for mom and dad?
Are you going to get mom, who's going to get mom
a $1 gift card at Starbucks?
No, you aren't.
Don't even tell me you are.
You know you're not going to do that.
What are you going to do?
For mom and dad, you're going to do something more
or from what you want.
have. All of us do that. We do that, we look at who the person is
and we will give something something, but it's with the
how much importance they are in our lives. That's how we end up doing that.
Okay? So do you want a one dollar Starbucks gift card? Would you prefer an
I'm an iPad.
Praise Him in the heart.
Metaphobus, theopisteus, chegapis, prosentete
With the fear of God, with faith, and with love drawn ears.
Thank you.
The Lord is the Son of God.